{
    "id": "1ddbcdd4e42e407abc0ed1d8fdb5ef57",
    "title": "Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The speaker’s .......................... voice put me to sleep.",
            "description": "Monotonous is an adjective. We need an adjective to modify the noun voice.",
            "answers": [
                "monotony",
                "monotonous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9ea4b99201684b689f1552d8022669b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Two .......................... sharks crossed the bow of the boat.",
            "description": "Monstrous is an adjective. We need an adjective to modify the noun sharks.",
            "answers": [
                "monstrous",
                "monstrosity",
                "monster"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2cda772f51464b1e80414859789a3721"
        },
        {
            "question": "Speaking down to the people was a ............................... mistake.",
            "description": "Monumental is an adjective. We need an adjective to modify the noun mistake.",
            "answers": [
                "monumental",
                "monument",
                "monumentary"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed764e5dbd984ab89002e36008df781b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bicycling is good exercise ............................, it does not pollute the air.",
            "description": "All of these expressions can be used to add information to what has already been said.",
            "answers": [
                "moreover",
                "furthermore",
                "in addition",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "b48e8ad73aaf48a5b8e158d7580e9077"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is obvious from his ruthless behavior that he has no ...............................",
            "description": "Moral is an adjective. Morality is the noun.",
            "answers": [
                "moral",
                "morale",
                "morality"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19a14cff4f5744d5a793a7a76c183330"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ............................. of the story is that money can’t buy happiness.",
            "description": "A moral is a point or lesson.",
            "answers": [
                "moral",
                "morale",
                "morality"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "69e16229ec90407f8bfb2db10e42b807"
        },
        {
            "question": "After the defeat, the army’s .................................. was low.",
            "description": "Morale is a state of mind in terms of courage or confidence.",
            "answers": [
                "moral",
                "morale",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "604661408ecf41f3bd500e45c16210fe"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. everyone enjoyed the party.",
            "description": "Most means more than half. Almost does not mean most.",
            "answers": [
                "Almost",
                "Most",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "785b96fa1e5a4ca4b4e3c23fbecd01d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will ............................... over your proposal and let you know.",
            "description": "A mule is an ass or half-donkey-half-mare. Mull means ponder.",
            "answers": [
                "mull",
                "mule"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea297347c2b64d32b30d27680cd18948"
        },
        {
            "question": "A ............................. of problems delayed the construction project.",
            "description": "Multitude means a great number of.",
            "answers": [
                "multiple",
                "multitude"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c522d7107f24f16838247087fbf922d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .............................. on the subject of faith.",
            "description": "Mute means silent.",
            "answers": [
                "mute",
                "moot",
                "mutt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c49be9bbcea24e128c0526e8d6af435e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ................................ was obvious from the way she told everyone her life story.",
            "description": "Naivety means innocence.",
            "answers": [
                "naive",
                "naivety"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1457bd1a80d9411f83b3deb7f71395b2"
        }
    ]
}